<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Roll For Pandas</title>
		<description>my boardgame experiences</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>The Resistance</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;Who are the spies?! The Resistance is a social deduction game. It is similar to mafia, but doesn’t have the player elimination mechanic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Summary:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Year Published:&lt;/b&gt; 2009&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;# of Players:&lt;/b&gt; 5-10 (best with more than 7)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Suggested Age:&lt;/b&gt; 12+&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Setup Time:&lt;/b&gt; 5-10 mins&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Avg. Playing Time:&lt;/b&gt; 30 mins&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Rating:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; $$&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Story:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A small group of rebellions are trying to overthrow the evil and corrupt empire. There are a few spies hidden within their ranks and the group must work together to identify the spies!   A new leader gets to send a specific amount of people (depends on the total number of players) on a mission. Everyone gets to voice their opinions and speculations. Then the leader makes the ultimate decision for that round on who to send. But, the majority needs to agree so there’s a vote before the final decision. Be careful not to send a spy (or spies)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Goal:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re on the blue team (rebellions), then you want to complete 3 out of 5 missions. To guarantee the success of the mission, you want to send yourself and your fellow non-spy peers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re on the red team (spies), then you want to send yourself (or your fellow spies) on the mission. You want to secretly sabotage the blue team’s plan by throwing in the fail card!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve played this game so many times with various groups of people and each time it is very different. There are also many different methods that you can change up the game. For example, you can play with the expansion with a Commander and Assassin. You can try playing a whole game with blind spies so they don’t know who the other spies are. Or you can secretly not put in a spy card and watch the world burn with everyone yelling at each other. It is definitely one of those games that is still fun and interesting to watch other people play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have a lot of funny stories from playing this game. My favorite was when we had our house warming party. We had a bunch of games out for people to play and there were a few new players that wanted to try Resistance. My fiancé, who is the rules master, was blackout drunk. He was sitting there on the floor surrounded by our friends while explaining the rules of the game. He finished the whole explanation perfectly and nobody even noticed that he was drunk . They were completely oblivious until he started repeating the instructions again. We played it so many times that I guess he has the instructions deeply ingrained into his brain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;“I swear I’m not the spy!”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen people swear on their die-hard fan status of a specific celebrity or band that they’re not the spy. Some people even promised to buy some kind of snack (or aka boba) for the leader to gain their trust to go on a mission. It’s hilarious how far some people will go to convince someone that they’re not the spy. The interactions that people have playing this game is hilarious and you might not get it until you play.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another story was when we were playing one night at a family get together. I was the spy 12 times!! Not just a few times, but TWELVE! We played a total of 15-18 games and I was the only one that was consistently a spy. The group was big, about 8-9 players so there were plenty of other people that could’ve been the spies. It was ridiculous how bad my luck was that night. I tried picking first, picking last, had random people pick the cards for me. It was just horrible! The game became boring for me after being the spy for 5-6 times because no one believed me after that. Not like I’ve ever made any outrageous promise that I wasn’t the spy. I guess I should’ve tried doing that! The chances of this happening is so rare, but I guess it just had to happen to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some people are just good at bluffing. I’m one of those that are horrible at it. So, if I’m the spy, I rarely get sent on a mission. According to my fiancé, I get very defensive when I’m accused of being a spy when I’m not. So, armed with this knowledge, I was able to use this tip and tricked him a few times. But Shhhh… don’t tell anyone my secret!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why I like this game:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It’s a great party and team game to play with friends and family&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Easy to learn&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;It trains me to pay more attention to people’s body language&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;There’s always a funny story from playing this game&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I definitely recommend the game. It’s a good introduction game to get your friends and family interested in the modern board games. At least that is what happened with our friends. Several of them have their own copy so they can play with their family and different sets of friends.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>/The-Resistance/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/The-Resistance/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Escape The Curse of the Temple</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;“Locked! I’m locked!”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is what you will hear a lot of when you play Escape: The Curse of the Temple. This is a super-fast paced co-op game- exactly 10 minutes long with a soundtrack to let you know when time is up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/Summary-Rating-Escape.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ratings&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price:&lt;/b&gt; $40-50&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Buy:&lt;/b&gt; Amazon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;GAME PLAY:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You and your crew were out exploring an ancient temple. During the exploration, you guys found some gems and decided to take them. Your team took too many gems and now the temple will collapse within 10 minutes. Everyone needs to find the exit out of the temple before it collapses! The door will not open unless you put enough gems back on the altar. That’s not all! Did I mention that there are traps? Nothing like a cursed temple without traps to thwart your exit plan! The traps activate twice during the game and you need to make your way back to the safe room before the gong rings. (Yes, there is a soundtrack for this game!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;font size=&quot;5&quot; color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;Goal:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Escape the cursed temple with &lt;b&gt;everyone&lt;/b&gt; alive!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_dice.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dice&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_gems3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gems&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Green gems&lt;/b&gt; – you need to get rid of these before you’ll be able to exit the temple&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Black mask&lt;/b&gt; – locked, you can’t roll that dice until you roll a golden mask&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Gold mask&lt;/b&gt; – unlocks 2 black mask, can be transfer to unlock other players on the same tile as you&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Green explorer, torch, keys&lt;/b&gt; – items that you need to move on to the next tile or to get rid of the green gem or curses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All players roll their dice and perform their actions simultaneously. You all start off on the same tile and explore the temple to get rid of the gems, while trying to find the exit. (Hopefully, in groups so you don’t get locked and end up alone!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_beginner.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;1st Round&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first round to introduce new players doesn’t have any curses (above picture). But once they’ve successfully completed the first round, we introduce curses into the game (below picture).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_wcurses.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Playing with Curses&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_exploring2.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Exploring&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
There are various curses in the game. If you can’t get rid of it then you’re stuck with that curse until the end of the game.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_curses.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Curses&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lost dice:&lt;/b&gt; Each die that falls off the table is permanent lost&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Broken die:&lt;/b&gt; One of your dice is broken and can only be retrieved after you have lifted the curse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Mask:&lt;/b&gt; You (or the player of your choice in the same chamber as you) can only re-roll 1 black mask for 1 golden mask until the curse is lifted&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Silence:&lt;/b&gt; You’re not allowed to talk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Cursed hand:&lt;/b&gt; Place one hand on your forehead and keep it there until the curse is lifted&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;Trap:&lt;/b&gt; You may not enter or discover a chamber&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_treasure.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Treasure&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
You need to roll 2 keys to retrieve the treasures. All of these can only be used once.&lt;br /&gt;
* &lt;b&gt;Teleport:&lt;/b&gt; you can move to another chamber that contains at least 1 other adventurer. The chambers don’t need to be next to each other &lt;br /&gt;
* &lt;b&gt;Double torch:&lt;/b&gt; serves as 2 torch icons &lt;br /&gt;
* &lt;b&gt;Healing mask:&lt;/b&gt; all adventurers may re-roll all of their black masks immediately &lt;br /&gt;
* &lt;b&gt;Double key:&lt;/b&gt; serves as 2 key icons &lt;br /&gt;
* &lt;b&gt;Extra gem:&lt;/b&gt; take a gem from the depot and place t on this treasure tile. It is considered activated until the end of the game&lt;br /&gt;
* &lt;b&gt;Secret passage:&lt;/b&gt; place this between 2 adjacent chambers that have no open passage between them (can be used by all adventurers until end of game)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not like trying to escape the temple without locking all your dice isn’t hard already! I think the curses and treasures make it a lot harder and interesting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;COMPONENTS/STORAGE:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_box.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Box&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_content.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Contents&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;starting chamber&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;exit&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;gem chambers (x4)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;basic chamber tiles - without purple masks and/or treasure icon (only need the chambers with purple masks and/or treasure icon only if you want to play the “Treasure” and/or “Curses” module)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;gem depot (for magic gems)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;magic gems (x25)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;dice (x25)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;adventurer figures (x5)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CD soundtrack and audio introduction&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;supplement for 2 modules “Curses” and “Treasures”&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;supplment for expansion “The Sand of Fortune”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_packaging.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Box&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think the box is a little big for the components that it comes with. There’s a lot of empty room in there so everything moves around a lot even after I’ve organized it neatly. I think it’s probably because we don’t have any of the expansions. To me, the “Curses” and “Treasure” modules don’t really count as part of the expansions. Even though they say they’re “expansions” they’re still part of the base game when you buy it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;LIKES:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;very fast paced - it doesn’t matter if you have a super slow player with you, the game WILL end in 10 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;thrilling – the soundtrack of this game really gets your heart racing, especially when the traps are about to be activated or the temple is about to collapse&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;very simple rules – new players can get into it pretty quickly&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;language independent - You only need to know 1 word: “locked.” You can play the game with someone that doesn’t speak English. Of course, you need someone who is able to speak the other language to explain the rules. Aside from that you can play without knowing anything else.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;LOTS of dice rolling! Of course, don’t roll off the table when you’re cursed with that card!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_offtable.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lost Dice&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;NOTE:&lt;/b&gt; I absolutely LOVE rolling dice! (if you couldn’t tell already…) The “Lost Dice” curse is like my worst nightmare. My friends comment on my dice rolling ways… that I sometimes roll a little to wildly and hard. But, I feel like my style makes my rolls better! Yes, I understand the rules of probability, but I just FEEL luckier. I don’t usually roll my dice off the table. haha… just knocking things over on the table with my rolls sometimes. Anyways, I never try to lift the “Lost Dice” curse because I feel like it’s a waste of time for me. But oh boy, it definitely bites me in the butt sometimes when I happen to actually roll it off the table!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;DISLIKES:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s nothing that I don’t like about this game. The only thing that bothers me is how the box is too big (as mentioned above). When I organize the box neatly and move it to our board game shelf, the components inside move because there’s too much room. It probably isn’t a flaw from the designers and publishers of the game though. The box is probably intended to be used for storing the other expansion packs, which we don’t have. Aside from that, I can’t think of anything else that I dislike about this game.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;STORIES:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every time we play, one or more of these occurs. Perhaps it’s just my group of friends, but I think some of these are pretty funny and wanted to share with you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Lone Explorer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_exit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Lone Explorer&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s always one person who venture out on their own and end up locking themselves up with all black masks. Everyone needs to be in the safe room when the traps get activated otherwise, they will get hurt (lose 1 die). So, someone needs to go and rescue this player. The player that leaves to rescue the other player could (usually does) end up locking their dice too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Consecutive Curses&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_playercurses.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Consecutive Curses&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There’s also another type of player. The player that doesn’t explore tiles because they don’t want to get cursed. Of course, I didn’t know this… I thought I was just super unlucky and got cursed EVERY.SINGLE. TIME! I’m usually way too concentrated on rolling my dice. I wouldn’t even know that they were waiting for me and didn’t attempt to explore the new tiles. I only found out when I said, “Man, I’m always so unlucky with those curses!” and they fessed up about never having explored a tile. I’m okay with being the explorer as long as the curses don’t all pile up on me! Oh, did I forget to mention? The curses can pile up! You can be mute, with one hand on your head, and have 1 less die!! Ahh!! How are you suppose to unlock yourself with so many handicaps!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;“Go on, save yourself!”&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/escape-pics/escape_almostout.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Save Yourself&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes you just can’t be saved and you have to let your friends escape to safety without you. It usually happens with the lone explorer, but not always. When the gong rings (signaling the activation of the traps or the temple collasping), there’s not much time left. Your dice could be locked or you could just be unlucky with your rolls. If your friends escape the temple before you, then they can give 1 player 1 of their dice. This allows the remaining player a slight advantage to escape safely.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall, it’s a really fun game that is only 10 minutes long. Want to make it more exciting? Play the soundtrack louder to get your heart pumping as you race against time to escape. Will you be able to safely escape this cursed temple with all your friends? Try it out and let me know what you think!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>/Escape/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/Escape/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Sushi Go!</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;You’re not supposed to judge a book by it’s cover, same rule applies to board games. But, Sushi Go! is definitely an exception. Look at how adorable this game is! The design is not only undeniably cute, it’s also super fun! By the end of the game, you’ll be craving sushi (or dumplings).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/sushi-go-pics/Summary-Rating-Sushi-Go!.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Rating&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt; $10&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Buy:&lt;/b&gt; Amazon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We picked up Sushi Go! last year to use as a raffle prize for the board game party that we host at our house. It was oh so cute that I wanted to keep it for ourselves! Don’t worry, I didn’t. I can’t deny that I didn’t think long and hard about it though! ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This game is so awesome that after we gave it away during the raffle, we had to go pick up another copy for ourselves! This is absolutely one of my most favorite filler games. It’s just so adorable, how can you possibly say no?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;GAME PLAY:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;font size=&quot;5&quot; color=&quot;red&quot;&gt;Goal:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt; During the 3 rounds of card drafting, you want to have the best meal with the most points! A meal is not complete without dessert so don’t forget to get your pudding!&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game comes with a total of 108 cards: 12 different types&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/sushi-go-pics/sushi-go-1_edit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;All the sushi&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;chopsticks&lt;/b&gt; - allows you to pick 2 cards the next turn of your choice. When you use the chopsticks to pick 2 cards, return the chopsticks back to the stack&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;wasabi&lt;/b&gt; - you need to place this down 1st before placing your nigiri. This card will allow you to x3 your nigiri points&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;squid nigiri&lt;/b&gt; - 3 pts (on top of wasabi = 9 pts)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;salmon nigiri&lt;/b&gt; - 2 pts (on top of wasabi card = 6 pts)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;egg nigiri&lt;/b&gt; - 1 pt (on top of wasabi card = 3 pts)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;maki rolls&lt;/b&gt; - the player with the most maki rolls win 6 pts and 2nd most wins 3 pts. If there’s a tie then you split the points between the players&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;tempura&lt;/b&gt; - 2 shrimp tempura = 5 pts (1 card = 0 pt)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;sashimi&lt;/b&gt; - 3 sashimi cards = 10 pts (1-2 sashimi = 0 pt)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;dumplings&lt;/b&gt; - more dumplings = more points&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;pudding&lt;/b&gt; - player with the most pudding gets 6 pts, player with the least gets -6 pts. If there’s a tie, the points awarded/deducted are evenly split out. So, don’t forget your pudding! No meal is complete without dessert!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Quick how to play:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
1. shuffle the deck&lt;br /&gt;
2. refer to the rule book to see how many cards to deal to each player (ex: 9 cards per player in a 3 player game)&lt;br /&gt;
3. look at your hand, keep it a secret from your opponent&lt;br /&gt;
4. pick one card and place it down&lt;br /&gt;
5. when everyone is ready, reveal the card that you chose&lt;br /&gt;
6. pass the rest of the cards in your hand to your opponents- alternating rounds. (i.e. rounds 1 and 3 clockwise and round 2 counter-clockwise)&lt;br /&gt;
7. after each round, add up the points (excluding the pudding until the 3rd round)&lt;br /&gt;
8. discard all cards into the discard pile except the pudding cards&lt;br /&gt;
9. deal the cards again (play for 3 rounds)&lt;br /&gt;
10. count up all the cards for the 3rd round&lt;br /&gt;
11. add the points from pudding&lt;br /&gt;
12. player with the most points win&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Examples of 3 different hands during the first round (so ignore the pudding for now)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/sushi-go-pics/sushi-go-2-edit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Player1&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Player 1: total points is 4 pts (2 salmon nigiri) + 1 pt (dumpling) + 3 pts (2nd most maki rolls) = 8 pts. It looks like a complete meal, but the sets aren’t complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/sushi-go-pics/sushi-go-4_edit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Player2&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Player 2: total points: 2 pts (2 dumplings) + 9 pts (3 from wasabi x 3 from squid nigiri) + 1 (egg nigiri) = 12 pts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/sushi-go-pics/sushi-go-5_edit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Player3&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Player 3: total points: 5 (2 tempuras) + 6 (3 from wasabi x 2 from salmon nigiri) + 1 (nigiri) + 6 (most maki rolls) = 18 pts.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;COMPONENTS/STORAGE:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/sushi-go-pics/sushi-go-box_edit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Box&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The game comes in a small tin can with cute sushi design. It’s very nice to take with you for traveling. The tin can protects the cards from getting damaged.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/galleries/sushi-go-pics/sushi-go-open-box_edit.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Inside the box&quot; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Also, there’s the black plastic card holder that keep them nice and neat. The instructions book is small and easy to read. It’s so simple that new gamers can pick it up really fast.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Likes:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Did I mention how adorable the design for this game is yet? It’s just too cute! I absolutely love it! My friends always comment on how cute it is.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Putting aside the cuteness, I think my 2nd favorite aspect is that it makes a great travel game. If you’re going to be stuck at the airport or in the hotel, this is the game for you. The tin box will protect your game from getting damaged. The best part is, it’s only $10 so you don’t have to be sad if you happened to lose it during your traveling.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We have some family members that don’t speak English fluently. They usually want to join in, but the games are usually too hard for them to follow. So, we always leave them out of games that are too complicated. This game doesn’t need any communication. You’re just strategizing and picking your cards. Super easy for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;We played this game during our engagement shoot. Since my fiance and I are such board game geeks, we had to incorporate it into our wedding. So, this game also holds a special place in my heart. (Stay tuned for a post on our the engagement shoot with Sushi-Go!)&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I love card drafting games! It’s super fun. This is a very light version of card drafting and it’s a nice gateway game for those that also might like it.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;font size=&quot;6&quot; color=&quot;#0B0B61&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Dislikes:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried really hard to come up with something that I dislike about this game, but I couldn’t think of anything. The game is light and fun enough for everyone to enjoy. There’s a lot of replayability. Everything that I can think of is positive. It’s just an overall great game.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>/Sushi-Go/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/Sushi-Go/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Love Letter</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;This is one of my favorite games to take on a trip. It’s small and compact enough that it’s very easy to slip into your luggauge - or better yet, your purse or backpack!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Summary:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Designer:&lt;/b&gt; Seiji Kanai&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Year Published:&lt;/b&gt; 2012&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Awards:&lt;/b&gt; 2013 Nastolkomania (Russia) Filler of the year&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;# of Players:&lt;/b&gt; 2-4 (recommend 3-4)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Suggested Age:&lt;/b&gt; 8+&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Setup Time:&lt;/b&gt; &amp;lt; 1 min&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Avg. Playing Time:&lt;/b&gt; 15-20 min&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Rating:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love Letter is very fast-paced so you don’t have to worry about keeping score before moving out to your next activity during your trip! Also, this game has very minimal language dependency so you can play with someone that speaks a completely differently language (of course after learning how to count 1-8)!&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>/Love-Letter/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/Love-Letter/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
