<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
	<channel>
		<title>Roll For Pandas</title>
		<description>my boardgame experiences</description>
		<link></link>
		<atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Love Letter</title>
				
				
					<description>&lt;p&gt;This is one of my favorite games to take on a trip. It&amp;#8217;s small and compact enough that it&amp;#8217;s very easy to slip into your luggauge - or better yet, your purse or backpack!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Summary:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Designer:&lt;/b&gt; Seiji Kanai&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Year Published:&lt;/b&gt; 2012&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Awards:&lt;/b&gt; 2013 Nastolkomania (Russia) Filler of the year&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;# of Players:&lt;/b&gt; 2-4 (recommend 3-4)&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Suggested Age:&lt;/b&gt; 8+&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Setup Time:&lt;/b&gt; &amp;lt; 1 min&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Avg. Playing Time:&lt;/b&gt; 15-20 min&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Rating:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Price Range:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Love Letter is very fast-paced so you don&amp;#8217;t have to worry about keeping score before moving out to your next activity during your trip! Also, this game has very minimal language dependency so you can play with someone that speaks a completely differently language (of course after learning how to count 1-8)!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I say &amp;#8220;boardgames,&amp;#8221; everyone thinks of games like Monopoly, Risk, and Scrabble. But, the board game scene grew during the past several years to be much more than that. There are now a lot more board games than just the typical/traditional ones that everyone is so used to. The wide variety of board games target different groups of people. Whatever your interest may be, you will definitely be able to find a board game that you will enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We live in a very exciting &amp;#8220;modern board game era.&amp;#8221; I want to share my board game adventure and experiences with you through this site. I hope that by reading my blog, you too will discover some new and fun games to play with your friends and family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why the name &amp;#8220;Roll for Pandas?&amp;#8221;  Good question! Aside from being an avid board gamer who loves to roll dice, I&amp;#8217;m also a panda lover. What better way to combine my interests!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Discover your inner board gamer self!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About Me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would&amp;#8217;ve never considered myself to be a &amp;#8220;gamer&amp;#8221; at all.  Not like there&amp;#8217;s anything wrong with it. Games just weren&amp;#8217;t that interesting to me. They didn&amp;#8217;t hold my attention for long, be it video games or board games. I never would have guessed that I would become a board gamer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Several years ago, my fiance introduced me to the board game world. We were at a party and everyone wanted to play this new board game that my fiance bought.  I agreed to play because everyone was raving about it so I gave it a try. Little did I know that this &amp;#8220;Catan&amp;#8221; game that I agreed to play would be the first of many board games. This one game was the beginning of my board game obsession.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We host a small 4-5 player board game night during the weekdays with some friends at least once a week. During the weekends, we host at least 1 larger board game party so we can play various games all day long. My fiance and I are the couple that bring board games to parties and introduce them to people. I tell him all the time that he should be getting commission or something. Every time someone talks to him, they end up buying whatever game he&amp;#8217;s talking about. Our friends started getting into board games as well so our collections continue to grow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, join me on this adventure to explore this exciting world one board game at a time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DISCLAIMER: This blog is on a voluntary basis. I am not sponsored by anyone so everything on here are my own opinions, good and bad.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				
				<pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
				<link>/Love-Letter/</link>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">/Love-Letter/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
